

andrew.bui.au@gmail.com

0413 116 885

Portfolio

Github

LinkedIn

Twitter

Tech

- + CLI
- + Node..
- + HTML:
- + Express.JS
- + Сссз
- Sequelize
- T 3A33
- + React.JS
- + Ruby
- + SQL
- + PostareSQ
- + JavaScript
- LManaaDD
- + iQuery

Tools

- + VS Code
- + AWS
- + GitBash
- + Photoshor
- + GitHub
- + Illustratoi
- + Heloku
- + InDesiar
- + Responsively
- + Acrobat
- + Balsamiq
- + Premiere Pro
- + Trello Board
- + After Effects
- + Netlify

Education

Diploma of Information

Coder Academy (Expected Completion Feb 202)

Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp

LISYD & Trilogy College 2020

Intro to Programming

Master of Design

UNSW Art & Design, 2018

Bachelor of Design

Summary

I have dedicated a year of my life to become a full-stack web developer by enrolling into Coder Academy and learning technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, ¡Query, Node.js, Express.js, React.js, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, SQL and MySQL.

With over ten years of professional design experience and obtaining a Master of Design to focus on user experience, user interface and human interaction, I have become driven to combine my design background with my passion for code to become a frontend focused full-stack web developer.

Projects

Portfolio | August 2020

HTML, CSS, and Netlify | My portfolio was the first coding project completed at Coder Academy. Challenges included learning the intricacies of HTML and CSS while also creating a portfolio website that is responsive on different devices and resolutions. A key achievement is an interactive hero cover image that also features a subtle animation

☐ The Augmented Terminal RPG | September 2020

Ruby | The Augmented is a text-based RPG that features a rich story-driven experience, looting system, multiple endings and a turn-based final boss fight. A key challenge was the initial lack of Ruby knowledge.

A key achievement was the implementation of the looting system, which steers the outcome of the game.

■ Weather Forecaster | October 2020

HTML, CSS, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Open Weather API and Heroku | The Weather Forecaster was part of a Coder Academy three day hackathon. Challenges included learning the intricacies of Github source control. A key achievement was being the only group that took on the challenge of implementing APIs.

Designated Designer | November 2020

Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Devise Authnetication, PostgreSQL, AWS Cloud Storage, Heroku Deployment, Photoshop, and Illustrator | Designated Designer is a two-way market application built using Ruby and Ruby on Rails that features an interface that is interactive between designer and client. A key achievement was being able to hardcode a messaging system from scratch.

Achievements

UNSW A&D Annual Exhibition

Master's capstone project selected to be part of Australia's largest annual showcase of post-graduate work.

School Captain

St Johns Park High

FoodieCrawl | July 2020

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Google Maps API and Zomato API | FoodieCrawl was a collaborative project to create a web app that allows users to set an eats crawl similar to that of a pub crawl. Challenges included the implementation of the Google Maps API; however, in the end, we were able to create a fully functional food crawl pathway. A key achievement of mine was taking charge of all frontend development, including JavaScript event handling.

☐ Game JAM | August 2020

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Handlebars, JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, Sequelize ORM, SQL, and MySQL | Game JAM was a collaborative project to connect a MySQL database using Sequelize ORM to a frontend using JavaScript, Handlebars, follow the CRUD paradigm and MVC framework. Challenges included inputting a large mass of game data into a database to access correctly. A key achievement of mine was able to create a fully functional and interactive frontend, including logo.

Experience

- Geovert | Marketing Graphic Designer December 2018 - July 2020
- Gainz Train | Creative Director December 2016 - November 2018
- Paintballshop.com | Marketing & Graphic Design Manager February 2013 - November 2018
- Action Paintball Games | Marketing Graphic Designer
 February 2013 November 2018
- Shopping Express | Graphic Designer & Marketing Assistant August 2011 - January 2013
- Fuse Franchise Partners | Internal Production Coordinator
 January 2011 August 2011
- Oxygen Clothing Pty. Ltd. | Graphic Designer
 March 2006 November 2010

